...
Printed, baby?
Oh, baby?
Let's see!
That's nice.
I like that!
That's very cool!
Oh, that's nice!
I'm about to do things in this game.
Things that no mortal has ever seen.
So the plan is...
God, I hate how that looks!
I don't like the little black spots. It makes me unhappy.
Now, there's something wrong with this map here.
If you look at it.
I haven't explored very much.
There's all this space.
And then we have an old man.
Cruisin' for a bruisin'.
And everyone is sort of centered here.
Um... yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Things are looking pretty dapper so far.
This is kind of a crazy community at this point.
And I like that. Where's my statue?
Oh, you know what? I think I put it at the old man.
I'm actually gonna take that with me.
Just so I have it. And then I'm gonna watch this.
Do that. And that's lovely.
Now, I'm mega excited because I found something cool.
I found a gray saponator.
And it uses mana. And it might be broken.
Which it is because... look when I shoot it.
Oh, wait.
Oh, I get the effect now, I think.
Hold on. Is it this one?
Create illusions and dodge and attack.
That's what that is.
It makes sense. I get that now.
I was wondering why that thing happened randomly.
Gotcha. So if I get hit by a brutal attack,
there's a chance to completely negate it.
Which is kind of crazy, actually.
Um, look at this. Pew, pew, pew.
It's awesome. It's very awesome.
However, it uses a lot of mana.
And I want to see if I don't have any accessories
that will help me with regarding that.
Uh, because I seem to remember having something.
Uh, now that's life.
Call me crazy. Didn't I have one of these,
but for extra mana or something?
Maybe not, actually.
Who's marring? Who's doing that?
Stop it.
Now, the star cannon.
I feel like I should carry that around.
In case I... No, I'd no. Nope.
Yes. Yes.
I should definitely carry that around.
And all of... This is ammo, right? Yes!
So we can even replace that shit.
Let's put the, um... What is that?
Let's put these in here for now.
No, no, no, no.
Um, this one is not a material.
Can I sell this?
Hano?
Ooh. Hell yeah.
Hell yeah, dude.
This one is empty. That's perfect.
I think I'm ready for my next adventure.
But I have an idea, actually.
I have an idea.
Uh, Rosalva?
So two goblets walk into a bar and one says to the other.
Want to get a goblet of beer?
Wow.
That's a good one.
So many others crammed into one spot.
The grass is doomed. I hate it!
I don't like Izzy.
He has no respect for other beings.
I hate lion, pines, the gulf versus destructive happens towards nature.
Here's what I'm going to try and relocate her
to the jungle.
Willy, the traveling merchant. Never mind.
Hold on a second.
Where you at, Willy?
Nope, down here.
Let's see what he has on offer.
You look like you can use an angel statue.
They slice, dice and make everything nice.
Oh yeah.
Code one.
The fuck? Devil horns?
Benny Warhol.
A chalice.
Let's explore.
The dungeon.
Oh, I just looked at the...
Hold on, I think I know what's wrong. I'm sorry, guys.
I apologize.
My bad.
I just saw a wall of something red and I looked over
on the little preview in OBS.
I apologize.
That's my bad.
That's actually a great idea.
Just spam the thing with lots of icons and I'll notice it at some point.
Thank God it happened sort of quickly, huh?
This would have been terrible otherwise.
I don't want any of this.
I could go for the bunny. You know what?
Let me take that. Let me have a Benny Warhol.
I will slap that somewhere.
Where can I slap that?
Slap it here.
Look at that.
We have bunnies down here and we have a bunny up here.
Everything is nice.
Everything is dice.
So I'm going to go to...
Oh, here's the thing.
I want to go here, I think.
I'm going to go there.
And then I'm going to bring Rosalva there.
What are you selling in?
Oh, you heal. Right.
That's cool.
Drisken.
Turn your crystal.
The first thing you need to know about are the special defensive artifacts I've got for sale,
but only if you've got some Defendant medals.
I don't have them.
I apologize.
Not yet.
Also, when I'm finally going to do this, I want to completely flat area
because I can't really shoot with my laser.
It shoots sort of upwards and it misses a bunch of people over here.
That's not optimal.
Oh, you know what?
Hey.
Now we can utilize our highway.
The railroad.
And then...
Hello.
Beautiful.
So here's what I'm going to do. I'm going to grab some living wood.
Is this, this is living wood?
This is just wood. Hold on.
No, it should be living wood.
Am I crazy?
Wait.
What's that?
Oh.
Blueberries.
I don't think I've seen those.
How do I...
I actually don't remember how to make that living wood stuff.
I wanted to make a living woodhouse for Reselva.
What's that sound?
Oh, look at that.
I want this. Living wood, chair and chest.
This is all wood.
Should I be using my axe here? No.
Also, the game is a bit loud.
I always overestimate or underestimate.
What do we got here?
Hold on. Something is popping.
Balloons?
Who's popping?
Oh, there's actually a house down there.
I guess I'm just gonna...
I guess I can craft living wood from normal wood.
Oh, remove that actually. Don't spawn that.
Don't spawn that either.
Statue bad.
I guess I could put Reselva here.
Is that actually gonna work?
Hold on a second.
Can I put them on the ground?
Do I wanna do that?
It's kinda cool having it on the ground.
Isn't it?
But maybe I'll do it a bit closer to the surface.
You know what? I'm gonna do that.
There's a red slime over there.
What the fuck?
Dude, this weapon is funny as hell.
It says might be broken and it's totally fucked.
I don't know what's happening half the time with this weapon.
It's amazing.
I wanna build a house inside of here, but a little higher up.
Oh, and that's way better.
Inside of here. See this?
This could work, I guess.
Let's remove that.
And let's see here.
Let's make one of these.
This actually counts as a table, right?
It's kind of a dangerous area to be in.
It's right above the... Yeah, you know what? No, no, no.
That's bad. You gotta be on the right side.
This is a danger territory.
That is no bueno.
This is better. This little area here is nice.
Okay, put this here.
Let's have a living wood thingy.
Let's have a chest as well.
Well, actually I wanna bring that back.
Put a gold chest here.
Why not?
Let's also take this torch and put it on the table.
Make it look nice at least.
There we go.
And then when he doors...
Let's see here.
I just need some wood, actually.
There we go.
Wooden door.
Actually, didn't I have a...
I'm gonna steal this door over here.
That's a much cooler door.
That's a living wood door.
In fact, can I make that?
Living wood.
No, doesn't look like it.
So there's a door here, and I can put one on the other side too.
I'm gonna continue this.
Make it look nice here.
No, don't throw it.
There we go.
It's a little bit scuffed.
But that's okay.
Let's put the door over here instead.
There we go.
We technically have a little home now.
So the big question now is...
If I go in here...
And I click on Resalva.
This room is missing a wall.
Oh, okay, right.
What is this wall exactly?
No, remove that.
Oh wait, did I not bring my hammer?
Crapcake.
Didn't consider that.
That's not smart, is it?
Let's see here.
I can make some wall.
But I want the same wall as this though.
Ah, whatever.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is this dirt?
Don't do that.
No, it's not dirt.
But you know what?
That looks kind of like a little patch job.
I like the patch job.
A little patchwork.
And now we, you know, just sort of finish this like that.
Yep, that looks nice.
Just like that.
Oh wait, is this not a wall?
Let's see now.
Resalva.
It's still missing a wall.
Okay, so maybe this doesn't count, but hold on.
I can put my torch there though.
So shouldn't that technically be a wall?
Unless this doesn't count.
Let's see now.
It's still missing a wall. Okay, fine.
Fine!
I'll get us some wood, I guess.
Actually, just quickly go back.
I want to bring my hammer as well, sorry.
And blueberries.
I can quickly give them to Dülan.
Blueberries for you.
Dye. Yeah, all these dyes.
I don't care about the dyes.
Unless it's used in some kind of
insane recipe.
Let me bring some wood.
There we go.
And what else should I bring?
Oh, you know what?
Hold on.
Didn't I have...
Who has the lip?
This guy over here.
Who's living there?
Lion pines the golfer.
Nope!
Nope, no, no, no, no, no.
That is not okay.
Replace that.
There. Give me that.
There.
You suck anyway, lion.
Oh no, wait, that's the other one.
Wait, spaget.
Lives here now?
It belongs to Drisken.
I think.
I think that's what that means.
Wait, no, I have the hammer.
Huh.
Well, okay.
That's confusing now.
Dylan, how do I make the living wood?
Can you sell me?
Living. I wish I could search.
What looks living? This looks living.
Oh, it just requires normal wood,
but it requires a living loom.
I see, so wait a minute.
If I just use a living...
This is the living loom, right?
If I just use that, everything becomes living.
Is that it?
Like, the normal things that normally are not living
become living now?
Let's see.
Oh, yeah, dude. That's it.
Oh, that's nice.
Let's make that.
Whoops. What did I do?
Candelabra. Land. Oh, my.
Oh, my God.
I think I understand this system now.
How do I make this living loom anyway?
Living. Toils.
I'm not sure I want something
that's living in my toilet.
Maybe that's just me.
Wait, living would work?
Ooh, cool.
Rosalva, this is going to be so nice.
Oh, I broke up one shot.
By the laser.
It's incredible.
I made my way through here once.
Okay, it's this one.
That looks nice down here.
Remove all this.
We're going to make it look nice now.
There.
Like that.
Yeah.
There.
Oh, my God. This is going to be amazing.
Okay, the monster sounds, though.
I don't know about that.
Maybe that's why this place was so cheap.
But wait a minute. Did I bring the living?
Oh, I didn't bring the living loom.
I'm an idiot. Fuck.
That was the one thing I wanted to bring.
God damn it.
That's okay. It's okay.
Craft my wall, please.
I think I had some wall at home, actually.
I don't want to see if I can make a living wall.
I guess this is technically a living room.
Oh, what just happened?
That was violent.
I guess I must have used my dash.
That's funny how that opens the door going through.
Yeah, the zombies are here.
That makes me unhappy.
Unhappy!
Okay, now we need a light, but I have a beautiful light.
Oh, look at that!
And we also have a...
this.
Oh, so nice.
Wait, can I actually...
Wait!
Oh!
Aha!
I see. Okay.
So I can customize my look here, and I can...
put things in the dresser, too.
Neat!
Sir, I've seen you.
Fuck off, please.
This weapon right here is insanity.
It's so weird, but in the best way, you know?
It does use a lot of mana, though.
But then again, the enemies drop mana when you kill them.
So that's nice.
Oh, it's because it's night, isn't it?
Is it night, actually?
Do I have my watch?
I don't think I have my watch on me.
Okay, man.
That is definitely a room now.
Rosalva.
Okay.
So she's gonna come here?
I wonder how long it takes.
Oh.
Man, I need to figure out how to...
Oh, I think I need to...
mow the grass. That's what's happening here.
Bro, this weapon is insane.
I'm liking it a lot.
Dude, I need pure...
Oh, this is great because she's gonna be close
to the crimson.
So I can buy the purification shit.
And I can start purifying the left.
We're gonna be purifying this entire world
and make it look nice.
You know what's great about the weapon here?
It's so fast projectile.
Except that one right there.
So it actually hits where you aim.
That's really nice.
I like that a lot.
I am a liker. I have been known to like things,
such as that.
I'm a known liker in this community.
How do I get rid of that properly?
I'm not happy about this. Look, it's sort of cracked.
We have to move it and then...
Maybe the hammer...
Maybe that's what that's for.
Okay, now the grass is gone.
Dude, Bro got pushed back a million times just now.
This is so irregular.
Also look, it hit the tree.
But now it didn't.
Or maybe I just hit the ground actually.
I'm not sure. But it's cool.
I'm loving this weapon.
Recharge.
Recharge my mana.
That's the downside the mana use.
It's so much fun.
I just want to shoot things.
Haha.
This is hands down my favorite weapon.
It's so good.
Okay, what am I doing anyway?
Let's see if Rosalva has moved in.
Maybe she is physically traveling.
Oh, she's there.
That's amazing.
Get him away from me.
The best part about this weapon too is that it penetrates the enemies.
Rosalva!
Have you seen the old man walking around the dungeon?
He doesn't look well at all. Yeah, I've seen him.
Tell me about your happiness now.
Solitude is sometimes good.
There's room to grow and to breathe.
Yay!
Status, 6% crimson.
Okay, so Rosalva.
I'm gonna need some purification powder here.
Give me like...
It's so cheap.
A hundred.
Be right back. I'm gonna go purify.
I'm gonna put that number to zero.
I guess that would require removing all of this.
It's not happening.
But I wonder if...
Oh, it's where I'm aiming.
Okay, I see.
Oh, yeah. Look at the trees!
Yes!
Yay!
Oh, but it's still bad down there.
I wonder if I can...
throw it from up here.
No.
Get rid of all the evil!
Evil!
Oh my god, this becomes stone.
Oh, I wanna try throw this on the enemies.
Be gone!
Be gone, evil!
Maybe it doesn't do anything.
What the fuck?
Nah, you can't purify the enemies.
Unfortunately, that dropped one gold.
Why did that just drop one gold again?
This weapon is immaculate.
Oh, wait, wait.
Evil is spreading!
Man, I can never pur...
Unless the goodness traverses through.
And makes everything below it green too.
Let me actually test this real quick.
Let's see here if this turns green.
Yeah, this is so funny.
Might be broken.
Rosalva deserves the best.
Why is this still red?
I don't like that.
I'm purifying everything here.
Is it spreading?
It doesn't look like it.
I kind of want to get into a biplane and just...
Spray these fields, you know.
I want to dust these crops with some good old purification powder.
This looks good so far.
Rosalva.
This is so nice.
Don't go outside. This is dangerous zone.
What's this about me having more bark than bite?
Okay, you're happy now.
What else can you do?
A pumpkin seed?
You know what? Let's try that.
Let's also... flower wool.
Grass wool.
What does this prevent you from accidentally destroying the environment?
While in the inventory?
I'm not sure why this is a thing.
I am curious about the dirt rod.
Magically moves dirt.
I'm too curious.
Oh wait, I can't buy it. I don't have enough money. Shit.
I was gonna buy it.
I'm gonna try and plant a pumpkin.
What's that? Oh, it's mana.
Okay, we're gonna have a pumpkin right here.
Let's see how that works.
Nice.
Keep the inventory nice and neat.
We could have a banner.
We could have like a dedicated banner section.
Somewhere in the evil lands, right?
Anyway, I'm gonna go down here again, I think.
I'm gonna explore this way.
And when it becomes night, actually I'm gonna go back first.
I wanna grab my watch, so I can look at that.
Oh wait, I had it in my thingy. Ah, here it is.
I had it in my loadout.
It's 9 a.m. right now.
That's okay, I wanted to do other things anyway.
Quick stack, gold chest.
Put it in construction.
Living wood chest, put that there.
Oops.
That goes in. The blueberries.
That can be placed.
Oh, they actually look kinda nice.
Let's have them out here in the garden.
There.
Beautiful.
Very nice looking. I don't like how that looks though.
I hate the railway.
The way it looks is not pleasing to me.
Let me quickly fix it.
Yeah, yeah, no.
That works.
Best I can do.
Not that it has to connect there, I guess, but yeah.
Okay then.
Is it time?
Let's let me see the others.
Hailey, happiness.
I love animals, naturally the forest is like the best place ever.
Yes.
Are we in the forest now?
I think we are.
Hano, happiness.
When I'm not doing business, I'd much rather be alone.
Yes, I hate feeling crammed in.
Oh no, the forest does not inspire me.
Don't like, don't like.
Dante the arm stealer has good eyes for vividness in business.
I like it. Yes.
Okay, so you don't want to be in the forest.
You're a diet trader or whatever.
Maybe you would like...
This place is very colorful. You should hang out here.
That looks pretty cool, doesn't it?
Or actually, in the sky, I could make one of those at home.
But there would be a fucking problem to get up there again.
Let me look at the others.
Dante, make it quick.
I've got a date with Catlin in an hour.
Really? Good on you.
Hey, I can't do what I do with so many people watching me.
I think Catlin the nurse ever, you know, checks me out.
So you don't like pines?
I'd really like to use Mortall the demolitionist as a range target.
So you like Mortall?
You don't care where you live, I guess.
As long as it's with Catlin.
You don't like lion pines?
So lion pines has to go.
Where do you want to go?
I'm not the type to scream and thrash around just because my ball lands in the water.
Sure.
Hate to say it, but I rather hate all the foot traffic here.
I like the forest.
It has all the necessary features for golfing.
It's always fun to hang out with Ludo the painter.
Good people.
Unpopular opinion.
I quite love having Izzy the Angler around.
I get my water hazards returned to me.
I hate Seymour the merchant's greedy attitude.
It's pretty unnecessary in a world like this.
That is quite an unpopular opinion.
Why do you love having him around?
But that's... I mean, I can move you both out of here.
That's fine with me.
So you like the... Is this the forest?
What about this?
Would it say, maybe?
A palm tree? That's probably not the forest.
This is just a tree.
I think this is the forest.
Even though it doesn't look like much of a forest.
I think it classifies as a forest.
So they can stay here.
Izzy? How about you?
I hate all these strangers.
They scared all my fish half to death.
More tall the demolitionist actually knows what they're doing.
Unlike some other people.
I kind of like that.
I hate Drisk and the tavern keep.
Anyone else who treats me like a child.
Okay.
Hmm.
What's your quest?
In the forest, the slimes are kind of gross.
Slimefish are even more so.
I don't want to swim with slimes.
So yank one out of the water for me.
Slimefish.
Caught in surface forest.
Okay, so that has to be here.
Thank you.
No, wait, that's not...
There maybe?
You know what?
I think it's time to go make a proper puddle here.
So it looks like there's something below me now.
Let me actually do this.
I'm going to make a little custom puddle here.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
Actually, I don't like that.
There we go.
Let's put some lights down here.
What's happening right now?
There's a storm!
Whoops.
Did it say anything?
Okay, it's just a storm. Interesting.
Oh, that's annoying.
Oh, wait, do I not have any...
I don't have any baits.
Dammit.
Here we go.
Ah, we've got worms now.
We should probably collect them.
But I'm going to fish this first.
Huh?
Goldfish.
Sure, I can catch you if you want to.
I don't like how it is...
I need to make this look better.
Oh, this has to be the place.
Nice.
Come on. I want crates.
Old shoe.
Bombfish.
Nice.
Slimefish.
I got it.
That was easy.
Hey, check it out.
You make a great air monkey. Now go away.
Thanks, dude.
Have a good day.
Okay, that was nice.
Put that away.
Sona potion.
Detects hooked fish?
What?
Well, I'm going to try that.
Put this bait in here.
And fishing.
That goes in there.
And the base I can use to make
nice buffs, I believe.
I just need the cooking pot.
Cooked fish.
Yeah, I just need one of those.
May as well do it.
Okay, man.
The golden... the goddamn golden key.
Actually, there's something I want to try again.
Where is it?
Meteorite.
Actually, just take all these for now.
I need to test something.
Oh, yeah, make all this stuff.
Contain.
Let's cook all of this.
I wish it would all just start stacking normally.
Lead bar.
Put that there.
Tin bar.
I have a lot of tin.
Not a lot of copper, though.
So I can't do this anymore.
200 is the max.
That's unfortunate.
This is nice, though.
I wanted to go... you know what?
This is probably the best time to fish.
Because it's raining. Right?
I'm gonna go in the... there's a big puddle over here.
I'm gonna go fish there.
I just want to do that real quick while I remember.
And then I'm gonna go back.
Let's test.
Oh, I love this weapon.
Rock lobster.
Look how atmospheric this looks.
Love the light effect.
Oh, I need to get rid of this.
Just so I can shoot them when they come running.
What? He got hit by it again?
This weapon is so weird.
Get out of here.
Give me crates. I want crates.
Oyster.
Shocked oyster.
Ah, shocks.
There we go.
Bro, this weapon is so good.
It's so much fun, man. I love it.
I'm so happy I bought it.
In fact, I'm gonna try to make all the weapons.
Just because sometimes...
they are definitely...
not what you expect.
And they can be better or worse than you expect.
Like this weapon right here, it looked kind of meh.
From the description of it.
But now it's like my favorite.
Just kill them all.
Look, sometimes it bounces off them.
Sometimes it penetrates.
Sometimes it goes backwards.
It's really fun.
Definitely broken though.
Quick, fish, fish.
Come on. Got it.
I'm gonna pick up so much loot after this.
Another...
so many oysters here.
A white pearl!
Yo-ho!
I wonder what I can make with that.
Wait, is the money disappearing?
I hear money sounds.
Which worries me.
Yup.
Wait. Oh, my inventory is full.
Oh, I got a raincoat!
Hold on.
Let's take care of these boots.
Fuck off! I'm fishing!
We need this.
Oh, shit.
Why did I carry all this stuff?
That was kind of a mistake, I guess.
Menacing sailfish boots.
The wearer can run super fast.
What the fuck? Really?
How fast are we talking, though?
Hold on.
Oh, god.
Okay, you know what? I'm going to go back.
I have no inventory, and I can't handle this.
And I don't want to use my...
mobile inventory right now.
Because I don't want it to be filled up just yet.
Uh, go back.
Throw that away.
Okay, let's see.
Actually, hold on.
What can I do with this?
Menacing...
Uh...
Spectre...
Spectre boots?
What is this?
The wearer can run super fast.
Allows flight? Okay.
Same as that one.
Requires...
Oh!
I can actually use both.
Increases jump speed and allows auto-jump.
The fuck is auto-jump?
So, here's the thing.
Tinkera's Workshop, I can actually
finally combine something.
So this will allow me to run fast
and fly at the same time.
Hell yeah, dude.
I'm going to do that.
Where is it? I put it up here.
Actually just looks like a dresser with some books on it.
Uh...
Do we need it unequipped?
Let's put that there, I guess.
There it is!
There it is, dude.
Lovely.
Another oyster... A black pearl!
Oh my god, hold on.
Dylan, I have multiple pearls to show you.
Whoa!
Yo!
Wait, how much can I fly, actually?
Okay.
But it's the same amount.
Dude, that's awesome!
That's like really fast!
I come to save you!
Damn! Oh, I got to get used to this.
This is freaking amazing.
Um...
Look at this here.
Lesson luck potion!
Yo!
Oh, that's a very specific
list of ingredients here.
Waterleaf, I think I have that.
Dude, I'm running so fast!
I'm not used to this.
Waterleaf...
Yes, I got it.
But hold on, we got, uh...
Uh...
My inventory is a mess.
Fishing.
Also,
let's put on the raincoat
for my second outfit.
Look at this! This is gonna be my Fishing
outfit, dude!
Flounder?
Uh...
This also goes in here, I guess.
I actually had some waterleafs already.
And then I need
water.
Buttered water.
And was that it?
Tell me again.
Also,
Black Pearl
increases the luck.
Okay, so this is actually just better.
Ladybug, I have that, I think.
Oh, maybe I don't.
Wait, wait, wait. Organic?
Yes!
I got one.
Oops.
Here it is!
A luck potion!
Dude, we're gonna go fishing
with a luck potion!
Um...
I wish I had another Ladybug.
Fishing.
Put that in there.
I wanna plant these
waterleaf seeds.
There.
Okay, so this one is obviously ready now.
How do I harass it?
I'm gonna...
So if I use this, it's just gonna get destroyed, I think.
But maybe it got destroyed before
because it wasn't ready yet.
That's it!
That is it!
Fuck yeah.
Okay.
Set to bring good fortune
and keep evil spirits at bay.
So here's what I'm thinking about this.
Does this have, like,
speaking of luck, right?
Does this have, like, a hidden
effect, maybe, of luck similar
to that potion I just had?
You know?
If it doesn't say plus
something...
Hmm.
Like, did this say increases the luck?
Set to bring good fortune, right?
Actually, hold on. Let me actually try that with
Dylan.
Can I combine this with something?
Where is it?
I can make...
Obsidian horseshoe.
Grants immunity to fire blocks.
And to make obsidian, you need water and lava.
I learned that.
How's the holder to quadruple jump?
What?!
No way.
Wait, how do I get a bundle of balloons?
Maybe a...
You know what? I probably have to make one of each
of these and combine them all.
Cloud in a balloon.
Cloud in a balloon, huh? Hold on.
Let me change gear.
Do you maybe take
cloud?
Is it even a...
It is a material.
Snow cloud, rain cloud.
Can be placed
prevents fall damage?
Sky mill and cold weather.
Alright.
That's interesting.
Okay.
Um...
So what else do I have?
This one is actually
also interesting to me.
Because if this actually... I was thinking about this last time.
If my laser goes through
like 10 enemies, right? I think it's going to work
on each. Which is kind of
insane.
Dylan.
Come here.
Okay. Stinger necklace.
Releases bees.
And dowels the user in a honey.
Release the bees!
Amazing. Honeycomb.
How do I get honeycomb?
I guess from a beehive.
So how do I make a beehive?
Beehive.
Also,
I can make it all kinds of things right now.
So, for example, these right here.
I actually want to...
I actually want to try this.
I want to try all the way. This one I've been eyeing for a while.
And this is... speaking of,
I've had an annoying hammer for so long.
I think it's time.
We get a meteor hammocks.
And then we delete this shit.
Hey.
Hanno.
What do you like an annoying tungsten hammer?
That's for you, buddy.
I know you like that shit.
Tin.
So the glass kiln.
I'm not quite sure what I should do with that yet.
Wait a minute.
It's magic damage.
This is melee damage.
Oh, it just occurred to me.
It actually specifically says the different damage types on the weapon.
I guess I never really noticed.
Like, this is melee, this is considered ranged.
This is not considered ranged. This is magic.
9%?
Hmm.
Interesting.
I'm considering making that, actually.
It's worse defense, but...
Hold on. Don't I have more?
Meteor?
Fucking hell, my inventory. Hold on a second.
We need to fix this.
Sort.
And do...
Whoops, nope.
Destruction put us in here.
Now, I have like...
How much?
Bro, where?
Where is it?
Am I...
Oh, it's here.
I see.
Okay.
I'm going to collect some more meteorite, actually.
Because I want to make all those things.
Did I make the gun yet?
Hold on.
I also want to test that.
Quickly give me the gun.
Oh, need to be over here.
Hard.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I don't think I have enough. I think I need like 20 or something.
Right? It's like 20.
Or 25.
20. Okay.
I see. I see.
Bomb fish, I'll bring that, actually.
Glow sticks are nice.
This shit right here?
Uh, sure.
Organics, put that in.
Okay, off we go.
Bro, this...
I don't even need to be on the railway.
I feel like this is just as fast.
Actually, is it?
The acceleration is definitely faster on foot.
But I think this is faster, for sure.
That's ugly.
Uh, where am I going?
Here.
Next stop, meteor.
Get rid of all this.
Oh my god.
It's all infected. Purify!
Purify!
Hey!
Shoot those things.
Oh yeah, one shot.
That's amazing.
Give me meteor.
Oh, you know what?
Bomb fish?
Bro, being able to fly is actually
fantastic.
Wait, it doesn't actually destroy...
Oh my god, I can't hit it.
Oh, shit.
That spawned right in front of me.
That's unfair!
Love this weapon!
Damn!
It makes me so happy.
I want to make it even better.
Oh, I wonder if there's a potion
that will increase my magic damage.
I just want to be the ultimate
fucking sapper.
Space H
assassinator.
Can you not do that? Thank you.
Man, fuck!
Huh?
What just happened there?
Ah, okay, it's that.
Falling on me.
I wish you would say, uh,
when I start burning.
But apparently that's not a pain
that requires a...
a little grunt.
That's just standard stuff.
Uh!
Let's get rid of that.
How much do I have now?
92.
Not bad.
Was I burning just now?
What if I do this?
Yeah, I burn. Okay.
I figured.
I hate these falling blocks so much.
They always catch me off guard.
You know what? I'm gonna use this.
Oh yeah, much better.
Laser!
Why are all these enemies coming suddenly?
Like, can I bounce it off here sometimes?
There's a small chance of it.
I can actually use it to shoot around corners.
Oh my god, stop pushing me!
I'm actually gonna die here.
Give me that.
My god!
What's up with all these enemies?
Fucking calm down!
Where's my thing?
Stop phasing!
This guy faces so much.
Oh, this is gonna be annoying.
Man, this stuff right here.
Crimson.
Boo!
We don't like crimson.
Luckily, I could just hit like a block inside of the other blocks.
And sort of circumvent it a little bit.
Not quite.
I have to sort of work my way through it, I guess.
Oh my god, here he comes.
Collecting this is super tedious.
Fucking enemies!
I'm done!
I didn't want to do this, but you're fucking forcing my hand.
Okay, I think I've got mo-
Actually, there's some over there as well.
I should save the bombs for the crimson.
Oh wait, it can't get to me.
Don't even think about it.
Oh man, that's gonna be annoying.
I'm not gonna get that.
Nope. I will get these over here though.
Okay, block this off.
Oh wait, I have an idea.
If we use...
Where is it?
Also, let me put this here.
Oh, did we use all of the powder? No, we didn't.
If I do this,
I can dig faster, right?
Fantastic.
Nice.
Let me just grab this.
Even though I have so much of it.
The lead though.
Always kind of useful.
Okay.
I think we can finally go back.
Actually, I want to collect those.
Thank you.
See ya!
Oh, so fast!
Okay.
Make a shit ton of these now.
Yeah!
That's lovely.
And then...
I want to make...
So how much does this cost? 20?
How much does this cost? 10?
That's 30.
Oh, and a...
50...
15...
9...
Okay, this one takes 10
and it gives me 9% increased magic damage.
And the current helmet I have is 5 defense.
Oh, wait a minute.
This set bonus here is greatly increased life regen.
Wait. Hold on a second.
Controls, hold on a second.
There was something I saw in the controls about set bonus.
Activate set bonuses down?
Wait a minute.
Let me take some damage.
Wait, I'm not sure.
Whoops. I just fucking threw my mouse
across the desk.
Somehow.
I don't know what it means with the set down.
Maybe it's like if there's an activation
you can do on some set bonuses
and that's down.
But this is just passive, I guess.
So...
It's not something I can activate on command.
It's just... it's always there.
So if I make this now...
Let me see now. This does...
50 now.
52.
Nice! It actually changes the
number on the weapon itself.
I really like that.
That's something, at least.
Since I don't have the set bonus now anyway...
I may as well go for this.
I'm gonna go...
Yeah, I'm gonna go full.
Looks nice.
Oh!
Set bonus.
Space gun costs zero mana.
Hold on.
No fucking way.
Oh, I don't... wait.
I do, I do, I do. I think I have some extra help here.
I think we have enough
for the space gun.
No, it's annoying.
Fjäll?
I need you to reforge this for me.
Only 38 silver.
Hell yeah.
A quick one.
Can we make it even better?
Again?
Unpleasant?
Sure.
I don't wanna waste all my money.
Let's try it.
Oh my god.
I may have found a new favorite.
Oh, the sound on that though!
I'm like a fucking space marine.
Oh, that's fantastic.
But wait a minute.
That's fucking... that's crazy.
It doesn't cost any mana then. I can actually spam it.
So that means...
the set bonus is hidden until you have the full set.
Isn't that interesting?
So the 3% increase damage.
I guess that's just flat across everything.
I mean, this is nice.
But I haven't tested it in combat yet.
Maybe it doesn't...
If it penetrates enemies, then it's amazing.
If it doesn't, then I'm not sure.
Let's go see.
Also, it's night. You know what? It's time.
I think it definitely does penetrate.
It doesn't do as much damage as...
the sapper.
But it's much faster.
God, it feels good.
Oh yeah, look!
Ooh, baby!
Baby!
Yes!
Meteor Man!
Oh yeah!
Wait, that one's pumpkin!
I got 6 pumpkin out of that!
Did I get seeds?
Get rid of this shit.
So, hold on. This does 2019...
I have an idea.
Where's my...
Let me put that there for now.
That's better, isn't it?
Increases melee speed, though.
That's not gonna help me.
But 24, 25, 20...
If I remove this...
I just got an arcane something.
Whoa!
Oh, I guess I don't need it if I don't cost mana now.
So 2019, right?
But look at this.
24...
Okay, it's actually a little bit random, I guess.
Yeah, I'm not sure it's working on magic.
The fact that it's like melee speed
could suggest that it only works on
physical weapons are not magical?
I'm not sure.
I feel like I felt a difference, though.
Just throw that away.
Remove that.
I actually want to test something real quick.
Where's my other one?
I just want to compare damage here.
In fact, I want to buy the one thing
that gives me a...
Fuck. Will you stop jumping?
Oh my god, I can't hit you.
There we go.
I want to test the...
Target dummy is the word.
And there's also an item that shows you the DPS.
Maybe I'll actually check that out
because I want to test these two.
Did I have that?
Shows DPS or something.
Oh, wait, I think it's a weapon
I think I can buy.
No, it's not Ludo.
Is it Dante?
Is it you?
Nope. Actually, you still...
Hmm.
I mean...
I'll take some bombs.
They are not bad to have.
You sell...
No.
Fuck, where was it?
There was an item that shows you the DPS.
But I guess I can just see it for myself.
The target dummy is up here.
Okay.
See...
53...
Man, this is...
Some good damage.
Did you just say 473?
Also, I'm not losing...
Wait.
I'm not losing mana.
Is that a bug?
Look, I'm not losing mana.
Whoa!
Did you see that just now?
Bro...
So this one...
It's like critting.
Sometimes.
But this one...
On average...
Fucking look at that!
I think this is way better.
I'm not losing mana with it.
That's weird. It only says space gun though.
Space...
A type of weapon.
Maybe it's all like guns that shoot lasers.
It's just that this is called space gun directly.
So...
I don't know, man.
That's weird.
I'm not complaining though.
Let me tell you that much.
Uh, oars...
Actually, that was another thing I wanted to craft.
Yep, that's it.
A pumpkin toilet.
That is the thing I've been wanting to make
ever since I started this game.
This has now become the shitter.
Since Rosal was gone.
Pumpkins for everybody.
And then we can auto-sword.
There we go.
Weapons... I guess accessories.
We put this one in here.
Uh...
On this one...
increases movement speed and acceleration.
Hold on a second.
Oh, I need to test with...
I really want to figure out if this works.
Probably with laser.
Because look at how slow we accelerate now.
And we're not actually moving that fast.
But with this, it's actually...
significantly faster.
This is a good... maybe I can combine.
No.
Maybe I can actually. Hold on.
Uh, dude, will you take this?
Okay!
No, wait.
What?
Anklet of the Wind.
Aklet?
Oh, okay.
What about this one, though?
Uh...
Don't drop it.
Oh, wait. This is not a material.
Oh!
Of course. Okay.
I see.
No, I definitely want these boots.
That's for sure.
And I think I also definitely want that.
This one, though?
I mean, since I can fly now...
Let me actually see.
Can I live without that now?
I think I can live without it, guys.
I know it's crazy, but...
I feel like...
I don't need that right now, you know?
I feel like I want that.
And this.
But I could also try this, because this is a material.
Fart in a jar!
Improved double jump.
Yeah, I still don't want double jump if I can fly.
Oh!
Whoa, I have that!
Hold on a second.
Right?
Wait a minute.
I have that.
It's a shiny,
but this is a lucky one,
but whatever, right?
Doesn't matter.
What do I need to craft it?
Fuck, I forgot to check.
Tinkera's Workshop, of course.
Of course.
Cloud in a balloon.
Now I have to use it, though.
I mean, depending how good it is,
rash cloud in a balloon.
Let's try this one.
There's a little balloon on me.
I mean...
But then again, this is also a material,
so hold on.
What can you do with that now?
Ah!
Quadruple jump.
This is how we do it.
Man, the fucking crafting trees here?
Are deep, man!
Jesus!
Wow!
So this is quadruple...
Excuse me.
All right, all right.
Um...
Okay!
So what exactly do I need?
Blizzard in a balloon.
This is a bundle?
Bundle of horseshoe balloons.
I mean, I don't have any of this.
I have that, but I don't have that.
Or that.
Hold on.
Sandstorm in a balloon.
I'm guessing I can get this
in the desert.
And this is somehow attainable in
the Winter Wonderland.
How did I get the cloud balloon again?
I think I got it in a chest.
Somewhere.
Or...
In the sky, actually.
In one of these, I think.
If I remember correctly.
But, ah, man.
Okay, quick test with this guy again.
Let's use the space gun now
because it's more consistent.
So between 19 and
25 at the max.
Now I use this.
So here's the thing.
It is possible that this target
dummy just doesn't have any armor.
And that's why this doesn't work.
Which is kind of unfortunate if that's the case.
So...
Fuck.
I don't know, dude.
I need a...
Something better to test this on.
But I guess for now, I'm just going to use this
because I'm not sure anyway.
It looks like it doesn't work,
but then again, it could just mean there's no armor
on these things.
But you know what? I'm going to bring it.
I'm going to take it with me so I can test in the field
if I need to.
That's the goal right now.
Put this in here.
Put this back in here.
And what else?
This one I want to sell.
This one I want to bring with me as well
because I can use it.
This one.
I don't want it.
Not right now.
Put it in here.
This one...
I don't want it.
Not right now.
The sonar potion, I want it.
Right now.
You're damn right I want it right now.
I want it.
Waterleaf goes in here.
Here.
Sort this shit.
Okay.
Let's go fuck up some shit.
We gained 8 extra damage on that.
Because of this set here.
And it doesn't cost mana.
Bro.
I'm so ready for the old man.
Bring it on old man.
Me.
Resalva.
How's it hanging? See you later.
I just want to kill things right now.
I am going to experiment with both of these though.
So hold on. 49, 45...
Let me try this now.
59, 48.
I should use this for consistency.
19, 20, 19.
I don't think it's working guys.
I think it doesn't work.
So we need to have the balloon.
It's shit.
It doesn't actually work.
Also what time is it?
3.56, so it's like soon night.
I don't know when that officially is night.
Maybe midnight. Or like 6.
Oh.
Nice.
I don't have a lot of armor now though.
I'm very low on armor.
This is the... I'm a glass cannon now.
This is the thing.
Not a no dude.
Also let me use this.
I made this for a reason damn it.
Look how cute I am.
Riding in this mine cart with my little balloon.
Actually, get off here.
I want to fish here.
Over there.
No, don't fish now silly.
Here.
Give me crates.
Oh wait, did I not bring?
I did bring bait. Good.
It's not the easiest thing to hit while you're in the air.
I'm not very good at that.
I suck in fact.
At doing that.
It's snowing.
See you Mercer.
It just skipped.
Man, there's no crates today, huh?
Ah, here we go.
A demonic snowball cannon.
Oh wait, I need snowballs for this probably.
Why am I so slow?
I think he just gave me a debuff.
Cool.
Bomb fish, nice.
I like finding these.
Oh, it's night.
Let's go.
Oh wait, I didn't bring my potions.
Quickly, go back.
Sword. Inventory.
Quick stack. Like that.
Potions.
Grab this.
Grab that.
And...
this.
Actually, bring them all.
This one.
Uh...
That's it.
Let's go.
Hurry up!
And while I go there, I'm going to prepare my inventory here.
So...
Campfire I have there.
The statue I have.
This one is for emergencies.
Swiftness, calming.
And regeneration.
And iron skin.
These are the potions I want to use in combat.
I wonder if I drink this, if it will increase luck with the...
Boss drop, if I actually get the kill.
Okay, we're soon there.
Also, my coffee is getting cold, shit.
Hold on, I'm actually going to...
One sec, I'm going to put this in the microwave real quick.
Yes, I microwave my...
coffee I didn't drink.
Don't hate.
Okay.
Remove that, nobody saw that.
Rid of it.
Close the door.
And let me grab my coffee.
Okay.
Quick swig of coffee and then it's time to fight the old...
Man.
So let's see.
Drink, drink, drink, drink.
And we are ready, I think.
All right, old man.
Here we go.
Shoot the hands.
I can't get past them.
Yeah, I need to be flying more.
Oh god.
Oh shit, don't go in here.
Why do I go in here?
It's a mistake!
Okay, I think up here is better.
Oh my god, I'm so low on HP here.
Oh no.
What is down?
Oh, I'm so low on HP.
I need my potion.
Two seconds.
I drank it.
Oh, I'm gonna die here.
Hand is gone.
What the fuck is that?
Heal me, heal me.
We're making progress.
Get on it!
See you, bitch!
Oh god, the fall damage is real.
I'm so low on HP here.
No, hold bad!
Jesus Christ!
Okay.
I think I know how to do this now.
I gotta be in the air.
Yeah.
We gotta be in the air for that one.
Definitely.
Oh wait, we can't try again.
That's okay.
Let's go to dungeon.
In fact, let's go to...
the one right below us.
Fishing.
Put this in here.
Put this one in there.
And...
The sonar is interesting to me.
This one can get deleted.
Potions.
These go in my... these actually stay on me.
Oh, I forgot to put sunflowers.
Fuck me.
I am an idiot.
These ones don't matter anymore.
I don't want that either.
And this one is not useful either right now.
I guess the space gun...
Get away.
Now...
You know what? The damn key!
Gets to stay here for now.
I put it in Michelinius.
Do not forget.
Gravitation potion also goes in there.
I forgot to eat my fish by the way.
I could have given me extra stats.
By the way, speaking of...
Yeah, it gave me two extra damage.
Look.
You know what?
I want to dig right below my house.
I want to see if there's anything down there.
Yeah.
We have a bunch of bombs.
I guess we'll put them to use.
Nope, shit.
Oh yeah, I think I see...
No, wait, never mind.
I thought I saw a cave.
What's that?
Orange blood roux.
Oh, right.
Just bob the shit out of this.
Wait, what's happening?
Aha!
Look at that!
Put the torch, please.
Thanks.
Look at that.
Load up.
Spore skeleton.
Yo, I kind of want to kill you, dude.
You mind?
Ah, that's so annoying.
Fucker!
That was a lot of work just to kill that guy.
Worth it.
This is it, though.
This is another one of those weird caverns.
Bob the shit out of this place!
Carbon bombing!
Oop.
Oh my god.
I want to bomb even more. I can't get enough.
I love bombing.
Ah, look at that!
Ah, I knew it.
Okay, so we...
But it's a material, actually.
So we can probably use it for something cool.
Something interesting over here.
Look at that.
Oh no, it's just a little
itty-bitty area.
With some pots.
Where's that spore bat?
Uh...
Here we go.
Hold on.
Hey!
Nice.
Torches.
I'll drink one of these.
Gold!
Mushroom pants and mushroom...
Oh my god, the whole mushroom!
Wait, this reminds me of Mario.
Is that a Mario reference?
I feel like that looks like those
from Mario.
Wait a minute.
Can I shift click this?
Okay.
That has to be...
Wait, what is this?
Cross statue.
Deleted.
Slowly regenerates life.
Okay.
Kind of want to bring this chest with me though.
Oh, take that.
Thank you.
Boot statue!
I wonder what that will spawn.
Boots?
Haha.
Man, I should make the...
Hold on.
Can I make that right now?
I want to make a scarab bomb.
I forgot how to do it.
Scarab bomb.
But they are so good
for digging.
What do we got?
Muds.
I can't believe there's this whole thing
right underneath the house.
I will take the tungsten.
Thank God the bombs don't explode
each other.
Oh, I just avoided damage there.
You saw that?
Just that.
Hey.
Fuck off.
What is that?
Dirt.
Okay, no mind. I thought it was something cool.
Did I just hit something up here?
Oh, that scared me.
Jesus.
Fuck.
I was like, that's a detonator.
Okay.
I need to be careful here.
Look at me. I look like an endgame character.
I have like balloons
and fucking spacesuits.
All kinds of crap.
Not enough to
withstand explosions though,
unfortunately.
What's that?
Oh, it's nothing.
Uh, here.
Is that it? No, no mind.
The slime is falling from the sky.
What is it with these slimes?
Falling from the damn sky
all the time.
Okay, let's see here.
Crawl that.
All of it was put in
like glass coffin by explosives.
Sounds about right.
Got my gold back.
I want to go to the right now.
Whoops.
Uh, no, dig up here.
Right here.
Some bombs hanging around there.
Oh.
What?
How did I just take damage
and what did I just kill?
Got the amethyst.
Ooh.
Wait.
There's lava here. I want to try something.
Oh, wait, I don't have a...
But wait, there's water up here.
I'm gonna try something here, guys.
I'm gonna try to make obsidian.
This gun is hilarious.
Remove all that.
Now digging up is annoying as hell.
But it's okay.
There should be water...
Somewhere...
Up here.
According to the map.
Whoops.
Bulldozer.
Ah, okay, destroyed tiles.
Man, that just gave me a fright.
When did I see the water? Ah, here.
It is up here.
And there it is.
Oh, wait.
We're gonna guide the water here.
So let me first do this.
This is gonna be so smart.
I'm scared.
Yeah, I was burning there for a second.
Oh, look at that!
It's sort of working.
Let me make a little...
Place I can breathe here.
Look!
I'm gathering it!
Yeah!
Wait, why is this yellow now?
What? Oh, is it because I...
Oh, I think I changed the biome just now.
And...
That changes the color of the water.
Weird transition, though.
I need air.
I don't understand here.
There it is!
That's got... I wonder if...
If that is inspired by Minecraft
or if it's the other way around.
I actually don't know which game came out first.
I have no clue.
What's with the music?
Oh, it sounded like boss music or something for a second.
I was scared.
I see a tunnel on the map here.
It makes you zoom in like that.
There's something below me right here.
I like this.
Sounds right right here.
I heard this one before.
Why does it... I thought...
This looks like a tunnel on the map, but it's not.
I've been baited.
I hear enemies.
Oh, whoa, whoa!
Fuck off!
I think we're in the desert biome now.
Actually, I can just check.
No, we're in this?
Oh, no!
Wait, I think I just got super lucky there.
I kind of forgot about these.
I think I just negated the damage.
I think I just got lucky.
Oh, it almost came back.
There's nothing up there, but there's something down here.
Oh, yeah, here they are.
Jumping around.
Those fuckers.
Let me just sit here and cling away.
Oh, yeah.
Will's wants some.
Scarab bomb!
Yeah!
Gimme. Oh, I don't have room.
Uh, hold on.
I think it's time for the thingy.
Let's just say...
Lock that.
Do not transfer that.
And this one.
Everything else can
go for all I care.
Eat that.
Anything else I should be carrying?
Hey, that's for you.
Oh.
Okay.
Here we go, man. I love this.
Let's go explore.
Also, let's be on the lookout for...
What is this up here?
Desert Fossil.
Let's be on the lookout for what you might call it.
I just got saved there.
What was I about to say? I forgot.
I forgot.
Dang it.
The bombs here, though. Scarab bombs.
Look how good that is!
Oh, be on the lookout for falling stones.
That's what I wanted to say.
Okay, seems good.
Now the map says...
Something this way.
Sort of.
Yeah.
I love this so much.
Something up there.
Do I want to go up there, though? I think I do.
Definitely my favorite grenades in this game.
Any falling rocks?
What is that?
Amber!
Very nice.
Nice.
Oh!
Slime has stopped falling.
I see.
Look at the chain reaction there.
Okay, that has been thoroughly explored.
What is that? An amethyst?
Hey!
Stop your shenanigans.
Bro, this one has some HP.
I'll go this way.
Give me these.
Bro, it's so insane that I don't
spend mana doing this.
Oh, there's stuff up there.
Go up here.
What do we got?
Oh!
Wait, what?
Bastard!
Ah!
Oh, yeah.
It's the best!
What is that up there?
It's nothing.
Nothing.
Alright then.
Look at me spelunking like a god damn professional.
Nice.
Let's see what's up here.
I kind of want to see what's underneath my
home.
Everywhere.
Like all the way to the top.
Whoa!
Okay.
That was kind of cool.
Thank god I didn't die from that.
Oh look!
They're taking damage from that.
Lovely stuff.
That gives me pleasure.
You confused.
Huh?
There we go.
Oh!
Money!
I wonder what determines that
for happening.
That's the second time now.
Okay.
I want to keep going up
and explore all of this right here.
Let's see what connects
this way.
Maybe a bit.
What?
Yes!
Exactly what I need.
Look at that!
What the fuck is that?
Ancient chisel.
25%?!
Bro!
I will take all this.
Thank you.
I'm going to equip that actually.
Um...
Let's replace that with this right now
because I want to mine faster.
25% is...
What is this?
Extractinator.
Placing silt, slosh,
or fossil piles into the extractinator
turns them into something more useful.
Oh no.
You mean the silt that I've been throwing away all this time?!
I mean whatever.
Whatever.
Fine.
Uh oh.
Be careful here.
Down! Thanks.
So there's also this sandstone workbench.
I will take the best statue
and an armed zombie statue.
Really?
Are you going to make an armed zombie?
Wait, when you say armed,
do you mean like the zombie has an arm
or that it's armed with a weapon?
That's what I'm wondering right now.
Oh yeah, scarab bombs.
Love getting scarab bombs.
Dude, I'm so slow.
Without this item.
Ugh, it's a slog. Holy shit.
Oh my god, hitting these small enemies with the laser
is...
kind of annoying.
That's why we...
I'm going to use this.
I'm going to get sand on our face.
What?!
I don't understand the effects of this weapon here.
That thing just killed someone off-screen.
Somehow.
Oh, thanks.
Throw the mining speed.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah!
Yeah!
Makes me so happy.
That is an insane
item.
That's basically the potion.
But all the time.
The potion also gives 25%, no?
Okay, I can get further up.
I got...
Please die.
Shoot again.
What is that?
You saw that, right?
Looked like a little face in the sand.
Gotcha.
I was ready for you, bitch.
What is...
Let's see.
And that thing just took damage.
Oh my god.
The mining speed, though.
Okay, I'm going to go down here later.
Also, I need to keep track of the time.
How much did I spend so far?
I wanted to put a timer, but I kind of forgot.
But it's okay. Two and a half hours so far.
That's fine. I can go for a bit longer.
I wasn't actually planning on streaming today, but...
I had a plan today that was cancelled.
So I was like, hey, that's Terraria.
Feels great, man.
I mean, doesn't feel great that the thing was cancelled.
But, you know...
Terraria is always good.
Will not complain.
Get out of here.
Another one of these. I wonder what I can craft with them.
I'm actually very curious to see that.
I'm looking forward to asking Dylan about it.
Roll away.
Look at that. It's a duck statue.
I wonder if this larva will become an ant-lion if I let it live.
Die.
What's that shiny?
It's just lead.
Oh yeah.
It's a cave there. Man, this...
This cave network is crazy big.
Let me just drink that.
Man, the confusion lasts for quite a long time.
Thank you.
Also, what's the time?
7.23.
Ah, crap. I kind of forgot I had to check for the time to fight the old man.
Well, next time.
Next time.
Oh, wait, I need to...
To the mining speed, though. Look at this.
Lovely.
Scarab bombs. You love to see that.
Do this.
Hey.
I kind of just...
Fuck with me just now.
If I just shoot, will I just randomly hit something off-screen?
Or I think I maybe have to hit something in the first place for that to happen.
Okay.
Oops.
Oh, there's something up there.
Snake charmer's flute.
Wait, really?
An anvil?
An arrows, okay.
Thank you. I will take the chandelier.
I'm also taking the sandstone chest.
I can just summon a rope anytime I want.
That's fun.
More scarab bombs.
Haha!
What's up, guys?
So many of them. Look at that.
That was a slaughter.
Hey, that's for you.
Oh, man, what a dodge!
Yo!
When you shoot an enemy, the thing goes through.
It actually lights up the path everywhere it goes, so you can sort of...
use that to estimate where there's a cave.
Think about that for a second.
Alright, are you thinking about it?
Now consider the implications.
Have you considered the implications?
What was that?
Gil's potion.
Oh.
Dude, compared to the beginning, I'm so agile.
Oh, look at that down there. That deserves a bombing.
Oh, no.
What is shooting?
Someone is shooting arrows.
Oh, it's that guy!
Stop, guys!
Why are they all here now?
These guys are annoying me.
That guy just got push-backed.
To India.
Sometimes they go flying.
It's like a randomized...
thing.
You.
Alright.
I'm having so much fun with this weapon.
It's insane.
It's the best.
It changes the game completely when you have a weapon that you like.
I just want to keep fighting things.
Oh, my God. Look at him hiding behind that.
Clever girl.
Okay. I'll check this out.
This is the smart strategy.
And he's dead.
A genius.
Hey! Fire in the hole!
There we go.
Nothing in there.
What's that?
Wait, the inventory is full.
Banana? Yeah.
Put this here, I don't need that.
Wait, that's a sand slime.
Sandstone workbench.
I mean, I kind of want that.
Where's the thingy?
There.
Quick stack and...
just put all kinds of things in here.
This one I want to throw away.
I kind of want to take the duck statue with me because I'm curious.
Oh, God.
Okay.
I can keep going.
So where am I right now?
I'm right beneath the desert, actually.
That makes a lot of sense.
It makes a lot of sense that it would be here.
Slowly but surely, I'm exploring the map here.
What?
Put it there.
Executed.
Like, sometimes it does...
500-something damage, so...
Like, 10 times.
Oh!
That was close.
My goodness.
Good thing I have a lot of HP, huh?
Fire in the hole!
Have fun.
Wait, I got a thingy.
Hit it!
Oh, thank God.
That was actually getting a little dicey.
Put it there.
Oh, no!
Oh, my God.
This place is dangerous.
I'm actually gonna die here.
Let's calm down for a second.
Eat the banana split.
TripWish statue.
Remove that.
I'm actually slowly running out of torches.
But actually, I have other torches.
Don't I?
Sort.
Oh, my God.
You can't get up there.
That's fine.
Motherf...
I need a moment's rest.
But that revealed to me that...
Actually, I knew that was something there.
I can see it on the map.
And we got a sniper.
But I'm also a sniper.
Is that a jar?
What is that in there?
Also, I'm taking all this fossil with me.
Apparently, I can put that in...
in the extractor or whatever.
And gain something useful.
Oh, that was disappointing.
But, I guess it's nice to make my...
Whoa, look at all these!
Pandemonium.
Damn.
What's the time?
6.52pm.
I think this is time then.
I'm heading back up.
Up here.
Let's go.
Old man! It's time for round two!
I also want to find out if I can make better potions.
Because these suck.
I have 400.
And these one only heal 100.
That's got to be a way to make better potions.
That's what I'm thinking.
So, I have my...
food thing on.
Let's put on...
swiftness.
Iron skin.
And...
This is only minor improvements, actually.
Nearby danger sources.
Hmm...
I think we are...
sort of ready.
Yeah.
Whoops. Oh, I'm soon here.
Okay, we're back!
Here's what I'm gonna do, actually!
I have an idea.
I'm gonna remove the roof.
Actually, hold on. Is this...
Ah, this is wall. Perfect.
No, actually, I don't need to.
I don't need to. Ah, I have a better idea.
I have a better idea.
Whoops.
Get away from me.
Like that.
And then...
Get up there!
Oh wait, I have the wrong items on!
I don't have my speed thingy!
Oh god.
Oh my god, I'm losing a lot of HP already.
Oh, there's small animals everywhere!
Oh, this is terrible.
I can't see shit either.
Oh, this is horrible.
Ah, fuck!
Dude!
There were fucking enemies everywhere!
I need to clear that shit
before I start it.
Ugh!
You know what? That's fine, actually,
because I want to make better potions.
And I need to bring my ultimate food
as well next time.
I'm so tired
of dying to that piece of shit!
And I forgot to change this.
Oh, it's painful!
It hurts.
Green brick.
Nobody likes green bricks.
Actually, click this button, will you?
There we go.
Wait, what just? Oh, the money went down there.
Food?
Where's my food?
There.
Major improvements.
Bring both of these.
Golden delight.
Awesome.
So that's what I need.
Now, potions.
This one can go in.
Where's my...
There it is.
Put this in here.
No, actually put it in the food one.
Otherwise, it doesn't make any sense
to have a food chest.
There's no food in it!
Now, grab all.
Because it's time to
play Q&A
with Dylan.
Dylan?
Can I really not make a better healing potion?
So this... okay.
Reduced potion cooldown. How reduced
are we talking?
Pink gel?
Do I have that?
I have normal gel. Do I have pink dye maybe?
Hold on, I also have my thingy.
Take all that
for now and then
click that one.
Click that. Loot all.
Click that one.
Loot all. Click that one.
Okay. Slowly but surely.
Construction chest is actually almost full.
This is also construction now.
I have deemed it so extractinator.
Right.
Let's try that.
Put that there.
And you needed
desert something.
What was it?
Desert fossils, yeah.
I have that because I've been
collecting it.
In here I think.
Cream sand.
Is it not here?
Michelinias?
I have no idea where I put that.
But...
This can be anywhere.
I feel like it's got to be in here.
Sand block.
It's like a square.
Wait, sturdy fossil.
Desert fossil. There it is.
Oh, this is actually nice.
I should have used that
before I had the set bonus.
I wonder how much this is.
Dylan.
Dylan, Dylan.
Oh, Dylan.
Fossil wall.
Wait, what?
What did it say?
Silt slash
fossil piles.
Do I have any of that?
Delete this.
Honestly, delete all these as well.
Delete all that.
Granite.
Ice.
Mud.
Sand? No.
Shell pile?
It says pile.
Hold on a sec.
Oh, wait.
These all require anvils.
Okay.
Maybe I just don't have that.
Maybe I don't have what it takes.
I just thought for sure I had...
What just happened?
Oh, did the thingies disappear?
The stars.
Oh, I wish there was a way to search your chests.
I'm losing my mind over this.
I spent so much time
looking through this.
Tell me about these.
Heart lantern.
You know what? Let's try that.
Maybe that's superior to the campfire.
Requires chains.
I have it.
And what did it require, Dylan?
What did I need to make it?
None.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
How close are we talking?
Oh, does it need to hang?
Oh, okay. I see.
Heart lamp.
Wait a minute.
I wonder if it stacks with the campfire.
Hold on now. I gotta test this.
Oh my god!
I think it does.
Look.
Okay.
That's a nice development.
Beautiful.
Now, what were the other things, Dylan?
Repaired life crystal.
Requires heavy... oh, heavy workbench?
But also ectomist.
I don't know what that is, but...
Do I... hold on. Do I have a heavy workbench?
I don't think I do.
Heavy workbench.
That seems interesting.
Sell these.
What else can I sell?
I want to place this somewhere.
This is such a mess of a house.
I'm gonna put it over here instead.
There. Have fun.
Okay.
Now, the potions here.
Glowing.
Hold on, pink gel. Let me see.
What if I give you gel?
Molotov cocktail.
Slime crown.
What?
Golden... okay.
Summon's king slime.
All right.
How do I make pink gel, though?
Maybe I need to find it.
Maybe you can't make it.
What's my thinking there?
Definitely make all these.
As many as possible, in fact.
Okay. Bring this now.
You know what? I'm bringing an extra campfire.
What time is it?
Nine... okay, it's still morning.
Ah.
Still got some time to go.
Put this back here.
Night owl potion.
This one, I don't want it.
Put it in here. Nope, not there.
There.
Desert fossil.
Tell me again real quick.
Wall.
No, I don't want to make that.
Show me the wood again. Let's see here.
Heavy workbench.
I don't have it.
Oh wait, oh wait, that's it. It's here.
I do have it. Never mind.
Never mind.
I do have that one.
I was like, yeah, I gotta have that one.
Okay.
I wonder if life region is better with these.
If it's ultra bright.
Maybe it's better if it's ultra bright.
What is the point of crafting this if I already have?
If I can summon it anytime.
I'm gonna try this.
Give me lead.
Let's see what the deal is.
Maybe it's just persistent. I mean, obviously.
It's gonna stay in the world.
Uh, where?
Oh, equipable.
Wait a minute.
Oh!
What?
Wait a minute.
Is it faster?
Actually...
This is faster though, isn't it?
Actually, maybe it's not. I'm not sure.
Oh wait, can I write it anywhere?
What was the keybind for?
Mount.
Ah, this one.
Oh no, I can't. Okay.
I think it's a...
cosmetic.
Maybe you can have different looking minecarts.
And that's just how your minecart is gonna look
when you're on the rails.
And that's all.
That's my guess right now, but it could be more than that.
Maybe it's also speed.
If you craft a better minecart, more speed.
Right?
In fact,
this is a material.
Yeah, look at this.
Fart cart!
I wonder if...
the bottom one is best.
Amber.
Diamond.
Hold on.
How many did I need?
Large amber.
Okay.
Oh, wait a minute. I have a large thing somewhere.
Don't I have a large thingy?
Large sapphire!
Sapphire.
Look!
Anvil.
Equipable?
Is it faster?
No, I think it's the same speed.
Yeah, it just looks different.
I can't tell.
I think it's the same.
Cosmetic.
Really hard to tell.
If there is a change.
Okay.
This one I want to put here and make
like that.
Now the live crystal.
There's nothing else I can do with this right now, I guess.
Well, I guess I could make another one of these
to have at home.
That's actually not a bad idea.
Just have one here all the time.
And for that I just need to go down here, I think.
There we go.
This one we can hang
in the center.
There we go.
So that one...
We have an attack coming.
We shall be regenerating.
And everyone's happy.
Okay.
Now, I just want to quickly check all these again.
Snowcoat.
Actually, I'm only going to take those
that have material designation on it
and check. Hold on.
Just to make it easier on myself here.
Otherwise, I will be confused.
And that bar goes in here.
Potions.
Strange brew.
And a potion.
Shellpile is...
But I also have this one.
What does this contain?
Jungle grass seeds and hay.
Okay, let's see.
Why is this here?
Get rid of that.
Dilan.
Remind me about this one.
Something crazy was here, right?
Hey! Wait, I have this now!
I don't have that, though.
I don't have that either.
Okay, never mind.
But good to know that this is used for
this one, Hand of Creation.
And this one...
Obsidian Skull.
Wait! Speaking of Obsidian!
Obsidian!
I found some!
Wait a minute now!
Where did I put it?
It was sort of bluish looking.
Oh, was it in my...
Aha!
Dilan.
Obsidian.
Ooh, here we go.
Wait!
What?
Hellstone Bar?
Hellstone?
Do I have any of that?
No.
Hellstone!
Dude!
Something tells me I have to go deeper.
Dig all the way to hell.
Uh, okay.
Wait, what was I checking again?
Right, Obsidian.
And there's also this.
Increases summon damage.
Wait.
Obsidian Outlaw Hat?
Obsidian Outlaw Hat.
What?
Health Forge?
Wait, is it not the...
Oh, it's almost the same thing. Okay.
Hmm.
Weird.
Tell me more.
I
can make an Obsidian
skin potion. Immunity to Lava.
Ah!
Ah! Furnace!
Wait, Obsidian Skull.
I needed that for something.
Let's make that.
One defense.
Immunity to Fireblocks.
That's cool.
Um, okay, Dilan.
Now.
What can I make with this?
Waterwalking Boots.
To walk on water and honey.
Right, 7 seconds of immunity to Lava.
There's just damage from touching.
This is all about Lava, huh?
Okay.
Grants immunity to Knockback.
Dude!
Uh-oh.
Uh, hold on.
Incoming!
Wait, what are these?
Devil Bunnies!
What's happening?
Can we keep the doors open?
Stop!
Dude, I am itching for a fight.
This is fine with me.
Look at these fools.
They're getting blasted.
Oh, uh...
Let me go outside.
Yeah!
Zoom out.
There we go. Now we can snipe.
Oh man, it's so small now.
Damn.
We got enemies?
Look at us snipe through the doors.
Well, this weapon is insane.
And with all these banners here...
He got ejected.
Dude, I'm so fast. Look at this.
Snipe.
Fleeting shackle.
Bro, I...
I feel like... oh, by the way!
Maybe I can do the wave thing now.
Infinite mana?
I'm probably able to.
Oh, yeah.
I'm still gonna be sniping everybody.
Oh, wait. I don't want blood moon.
Uh...
I want old man!
Okay, we're going old man.
Old man!
Fuck the blood moon.
Hop!
See ya, buddy!
We're going old man!
By the way, maybe I should fight zoomed out with the old man.
Let's go!
Uh, so now...
Hold on, where am I right now?
Soon there.
I'm gonna eat...
Spaghetti.
Then I'm gonna eat a nut owl.
I'm gonna eat this.
And this.
And we have a heart lantern we need to place.
I'm just gonna put these banners down as well.
Uh...
Let's see here.
Everything should be ready.
I think we are good.
Yes.
Snipe these fools.
Also, I'm gonna light up the entire place.
There?
Lantern?
Hold on, I need to...
I can put that down here.
Where is the lantern?
There it is.
Place it there.
Okay, let me clean these real quick and then it's time.
Oh, you know what? I have a...
Oh my god, I just realized.
I just realized something.
Something that will solve all my problems.
I can't believe I didn't think of this earlier.
Remove all this.
Man, what's up with all the enemies?
Is it because of the blood moon?
I thought it was only at my house.
Okay.
This is gonna be a shit show.
There's no way I can do this, I think.
There's too many enemies.
It's bullshit.
I mean, honestly...
Fuck it, I'm here.
May as well try, right? I'm probably gonna die, but...
Oh yeah, by the way, so this is what I was thinking.
We're gonna use this instead.
Ah, fuck off, will ya?
Oh my god!
Where is it? There.
I'm losing my damn mind.
Why am I being pushed?
Oh, I understand what it is.
It's the stupid double tap thingy.
I hate that mechanic.
Let me have a key-bind for it instead.
Okay, here we go.
Old man, here we go.
Oh yeah, it's much better, I can see shit now.
Trying to hit the hands.
Okay, it's going pretty well.
Oh, I'm losing a lot of HP though.
Oh, I almost got hit there.
Oh shit.
I think I'm taking a lot of fall damage here from...
Yeah, falling.
Also, I'm almost dead.
Yeah, there it is.
God damn it.
I didn't expect to win this during the Blood Moon.
I take too much fall damage.
Wait, what?
Oh, I got a Blood Tier, another one.
So wait, is it still Blood Moon?
Yeah, I think it is.
Whoops, no!
That was not my intention.
Just clean that up real quick.
Nobody saw that.
Thank you.
Good thing I can't hit my friends with the laser, huh?
That would have been disastrous.
Heal.
What is this now? A goblin army is a...
Bro, can I get a...
Break!
It's like, all constant.
Let me fill up this.
Oh yeah, I was testing that.
I'm gonna leave that here for now.
Zombie banner.
Oh, we already have one.
Let's delete it.
Okay, let's get ready.
Quick shackle.
Cool.
Is it gonna appear here?
Where are thou?
Oh, here we go.
What's up, fools?
Look at me sniping.
Bro, the infinite...
mana here is doing wonders for me.
Goblin peon banner.
Let's put that there.
Why can't I...
Ah, it's not even.
There it is.
Oh god, I'm in a bad spot.
Also, I can't...
Honestly, it's being so zoomed out.
It's killer confusing.
Goblin's...
Man, I'm getting all the banners.
Hey, you there.
Have fun down there.
He didn't even die.
This gun is amazing.
With all the money I'm getting.
Yay!
I want a trader to come by now.
They're all falling in this hole.
How's it hanging over here?
Oh, you're chilling!
Lovely, I'm out defending the home instead.
All you guys are chilling.
That's great.
Oh, you're right there.
Nice.
55% cleared.
What's that?
The Monarch Harpoon.
The Monafadoo.
Fucking goblins.
Sometimes they get just thrown into the air by this gun.
Very weird.
I still don't think I have the power
to actually defeat those waves.
Because that's kind of insane.
But maybe I do. I'm not sure.
With infinite ammo like this.
It's very possible.
I'm gonna try using this some more.
Oh my god.
I feel like they should learn their lesson by now.
Do not approach this camp that we have here.
You're gonna get wrecked.
You guys are chilling?
Great.
83%. Come on.
50th Goblin Thief.
Goblin Warrior Banner.
I feel like I should put...
Can I hang that on a tree?
No.
There we go.
Anyone left?
Any stragglers?
Okay.
There we go.
Beautiful.
That was pretty neat.
What do we get?
Let's put this stuff here.
All the banners.
And I think that's it.
Now, Armored Obsidian Skull Dylan.
I need to get some more information
about this.
And I mean right now.
Now, let's see.
Immunity to knockback.
I mean...
It's a material, so I think it's worth crafting.
Oh, I can't even...
Wait, can I actually make it?
No, I need that. I don't even have that. Never mind.
But this...
I can actually make this.
This is not a material.
So this is a final result.
What's this? Lava charm?
Something tells me, if I dig really deep...
I'm gonna find, well, first of all, lots of lava,
but a lot of fire blocks.
So that's why there are so many items
that gives me the ability to withstand fire damage.
Also, look at all these shackles.
Maybe I don't need that many.
Uh...
What?
You are actually not the one I wanted to talk about.
Hold on a second.
Dante?
No? Who was it?
Is it you?
Morton?
No?
Oh no, you're questing.
Never mind. I don't want your quest.
You know what?
I think maybe I can color my gel
with this.
I need pink gel.
Maybe I can't.
Oh no.
Hmm...
This one is actually pretty sick.
It's not as good as the one I have,
but it's pretty good.
Uh...
So this one I can make, this one.
Oh wait, now I know what I wanted to do.
Fuck, I remember finally.
Oh, but I can't.
In my mind, I was like,
oh, we can make obsidian bars.
But we need to make
hellstone bars.
Which requires obsidian, but we need
hellstone, and I don't have that.
God! Dammit!
Alright.
Oh, don't drop it.
What is all this again?
Why would you want that?
Okay, nothing there.
Well, I think
I honestly just want to go deep
and find some hellstone.
And I'm talking
really deep.
So I'm talking scarab bombs up the wazoo.
And I mean straight down.
Presumably, this
doesn't go any further than here.
What just happened there?
This one just went crazy.
Spaghetti just went crazy. Why spaghetti over here?
The clumsy slime.
Yeah.
Oh, wait. Oh!
Wait, I've been all the way down here.
I kind of forgot about that.
I don't want to go...
Spaghetti went crazy again.
Okay, I'm going to go straight down.
It's time to go straight down.
Woop.
And all of this looks good.
I want this
here.
And then I'm going to switch back
when I need to.
Is there anything else I should be bringing?
Oh, wait. I can leave these bottles here.
And this one goes in here.
This one goes in there.
Spiky ball goes to the shop.
Archer banner. Let's put this here.
This one.
Put it.
Actually, I'm bringing this.
Yeah, I'm bringing this.
Immunity to fire blocks?
Yeah. If I'm going deep
and there's fire
seems like a good thing to do.
Now, Hano.
How about these, huh?
You like that?
Wait, I also have things in here.
Remove that.
Loot all.
So here.
Here.
There we go. Look at this.
This looks so nice.
Now I just need to mentally
remember what each type of chest
contains.
Sandstone, workbench, mushroom.
Oh, mushroom chest.
Uh, oh, I actually did.
There.
Look at that. Everything is custom now.
Isn't that cool?
I think it's cool.
Hardened sand
and mud.
Uh, that's construction.
We have organics.
glowing mushrooms, baby.
That's a lot.
Uh, then we have this one.
And I think we're about ready.
This one I can stay behind.
This one I'm saving.
But I'm keeping it on me.
Because if I need to get to the...
No.
What's the time?
Actually,
it's about time for the old man.
And this time, no blood moon.
So you know what?
Let's do that now.
Iron skin, swiftness.
Major improvements to all stats.
Sunflower I'm going to remember this time.
In.
Yep.
We're going. Fuck it.
See you later, peeps.
Maybe I am faster.
It feels faster.
Doesn't it?
Am I crazy?
It could be placebo.
16...
Wait, it's only been 16 minutes?
I feel like it was way longer.
Maybe I'm crazy.
What happens if I do this while I...
See ya!
That's what I expected.
This time, though, there's not going to be any pesky enemies everywhere.
Oh, give me all that gold.
There's gold over here, too.
No, that's silver.
Oh, I just had a great idea, actually.
Dude, I can make multiple stages here.
Wait a minute.
Fall damage, right?
Fuck, how do I start it?
I guess I start from here.
Please just die.
Daddy's building.
Oh my god, they just won't stop coming.
Okay, quick.
No!
You idiot!
Ah!
I swear to god.
The smart thingy is not smart at all.
It's stupid.
Oh my god, let me...
Let me build this in peace.
I'm slowly losing my marbles.
Get rid of that.
Yes!
Because look at this.
If I fly up, I'm going to land on this
and take less fall damage.
This seems so silly.
I've built so much crap here.
I mean look at this, I have like...
This is jankiest fuck.
What I've got going on here.
And it's all in the name of killing this fucking guy.
I'm terrible.
Please fuck off.
It's time. Okay, drink this.
Drink this.
Sunflower.
There, there, there, there.
Let's just put a bunch.
Get rid of that.
Do I need to do anything else?
Golden delight.
And... oh.
No.
The rest seems good.
Okay, here we go.
Old man, let's go!
Shoot the hands.
Oh god.
Okay, we have been healing.
We've healed a little bit.
Oh god.
I can also just drop down actually.
Instead of jumping every time,
I can sort of just fall.
Like when he comes here.
Yeah, that works pretty well actually.
Hit the hands. Fall.
Yay! Look at this!
I'm going in circles!
Oh god.
Oh, I can't hit anything.
Oh, I'm terrible.
Hit the hands.
Okay.
I'm losing HP here.
Ah! Stop!
Menus!
I think hand is gone here.
Hands are gone. Hands are gone.
Oh god. He shoots things.
My stupid minimap is annoying me right now.
Ah, it's clicking on the bar!
I don't know if I'm hitting anything.
Oh god. I'm getting hit by all kinds of shit.
Oh, dodge the protectiles.
I need 20 more seconds.
He's spinning to win.
Yes!
I have done it! The old man!
Oh!
Let's not die now.
Hold on. I need to get to safety right now.
Lock it up!
Okay.
All right.
And that's it for now.
Thanks for watching.
I'm kidding.
Let's take a look.
Tentacle spike.
Let's try that.
Oh, okay.
Mealy weapon.
Skeletron mask.
Violent bone glove.
Shoots crossbones at enemies
while you are in the battle.
You are attacking.
Oh, yeah.
Expert?
Oh, is this one of the items that is only available in Expert?
That's why I chose this, actually, because it said
special items or something.
Is this finally me getting the thing I asked for?
Let's see here.
Whoops.
Oh, yeah. It actually...
It actually does shoot things.
Is it with any weapon?
Oh, yeah, look.
Hold on.
Wait, even when I...
use my axe, it doesn't...
Whoops.
Hold on a second.
How good is that?
22 damage.
It's not fantastic, but, you know,
better than nothing, I guess.
But actually, is it better than nothing?
4% melee speed?
I mean, I'm not doing melee.
Hmm.
I think it's good for AoE.
But I'm already pretty good at that.
Let's see here.
What else did I get?
I was expecting something like
crimtane or...
demon eye banner.
Look at that.
The sign of victory.
We shall now wear his face.
Face monsters?
How about face me?
I am the face monster.
Look at me.
Get rid of that.
All the evidence is to be removed.
Also, what time is it?
Okay, yeah, three and a half hours.
I think this is the time to stop.
I'm so glad I finally got that guy, man.
That took so long for me.
And you know what?
This right here?
It's sort of what did it.
Realizing that I go like this.
Up.
Around.
Down.
Up.
That was the trick.
Let me light this up real quick.
Okay.
Settings.
Save and exit.
People!
A glorious day is upon us.
For I have finally defeated
the flying skeleton man.
The printer claims another victim.
Hey, LAVY.
It was a good hunt and for many,
Oliver's, it was their last.
But Skeletron will foul the lands no more
and it was all worth it.
Yep.
Indeed.
Fuck Skeletron.
Skeletron ain't shit.
Very good stream. Nice.
And so, thank you.
And thank you, LAVY, for that donation.
That's very nice of you.
Once again.
You progressed so much this stream.
Yes, I did.
Finally got
that fucking skeleton.
I am so happy about that.
He was just a pain in my ass.
What do you plan to do next time?
I don't know.
My plan is to have fun.
I'm just gonna do whatever. I don't know.
We'll have to see.
Magic Maki. Congrats.
Oh, Jen. Thank you, Jen.
Thank you so much, Jen.
Have you ever played No Man's Sky?
I've played a little bit of it with my friend, Peter.
And not too much, though.
It's been a couple of years.
And I know they have a lot of updates.
Maybe I'll try it once more in the future.
I think we played for like two hours, I want to say.
Not very long.
I almost don't remember much of it.
But it was a little bit...
Maybe I needed to give it a bigger chance.
But it wasn't that exciting at the time.
I felt a little bit aimless.
But who knows?
They have been adding a lot of content.
I know that.
Getting those speedy boots was really nice.
Definitely limenade.
Bloodborne upload.
Yeah, that should go online in like 15 minutes, automatically.
Macalaro.
So, look forward to that.
Have you heard of Return of the Obra Dinn?
That game is extremely up your alley.
Feels like watching.
I like your name.
I already played it, man. It's on my channel.
Check out the playlist for Return of the Obra Dinn.
That was a difficult game.
That game kicked my ass, though.
I had troubles with that game.
But only because I took long breaks in between sessions,
which was a major mistake.
I shouldn't have done that, because I forgot clues and stuff.
Yeah, I fucked that one up.
It was still fun, though. I had a lot of fun with it.
Have you played Terraria? I think you might like it.
No, what is that?
When tunic playthrough?
I don't know. At some point.
At some point, not too far off, I want to say.
My plan right now is...
I've been having a lot of work,
and I've been finding every excuse I can to play Terraria right now.
Bloodborne is finished, for me.
I'm going to play what you might call it...
Inscription. After that.
That's going to be the next game.
And then after that, who knows.
Probably one of the...
Second highest, maybe even a Subnautica Blow Zero, actually.
I think it's finally time.
But don't take my... It depends what I'm in the mood for
when I'm done with inscription.
And I can't guarantee it at this point.
It's just how I feel at the time.
And Tunic should come...
Somewhere after that, I think.
Unless I suddenly feel an urge to play Tunic, you know?
Then it'll just happen.
Inscription so hyped. Nice.
Yeah, a lot of people think it's great.
I love Tuna!
I love Tuna as well, Ubsche.
Should make it, actually.
Anyway, guys, I'm going to be jumping off here.
Thanks again for watching.
This has been a blast and I made so much progress.
I'm happy about it.
I'm excited for what's to come next.
I am excited.
I'll see you in the next video.
Enjoy Bloodborne!